https://www.runwildmissoula.org/runwild/index.php/fuseaction/about.privacy.htm

LoginHide Login
Username: Password:Forgot Password?
Members
JOIN!
DonateHistoryCharitable GivingSponsorsRace Equipment RentalPress RoomRace Cancellation PolicyPrivacy Policy
Join Us!Welcome1200/2000 Mile ClubRacemakers - 7 Races for a GoodieRun WilderDiscounts & FreebiesAnnual Meeting AwardsAnnual Meeting of MembersNewsletterMember Spotlight NominationVolunteer IncentivesLogin
Ask a CoachBack of the PackGroup RunsLast Wednesday Beer RunMonthly BOP SocialTuesday Track
Club Race ArchiveRun for MissoulaTony Banovich Memorial Run2021 Resolution Run2021 Calendar of Races
RWM ApparelRWM AccessoriesMontana Trail CrewMissoula Marathon
About Us
Blog
Shop
Calendar
Contact
Home > About Us > Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
Run Wild Missoula respects the privacy of all users who visit this site. No effort is made to identify individuals without their prior knowledge and approval. The following policies are in effect for all of the web pages owned and operated by us:
PERSONAL INFORMATION: On some of our input forms we ask users to provide their name, e-mail address, and/or other information for the intended purpose of the form. Whenever the identity of a visitor is requested, we clearly indicate the purpose of the request and the information is only used for the stated purpose of the form. Your personal information, including your e-mail address, will never be sold to a third party.
MAILING LISTS: If you voluntarily sign up for any of our mailing lists your email address or street address will only be used for this purpose and will never be given or sold to any third parties. This site maintains a strict "no-spam" policy and only sends email to those who have specifically asked us to do so. You may easily be removed from our list at any time by using our contact form.
LOG FILES: When a visitor views any of our pages, like all web servers, our system logs the visitor's IP address. We collect the IP address in order to compile information on what pages visitors successfully access, and what pages they may have experienced any technical difficulties with. This allows us to make improvements and upgrades to the site as needed. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is completely anonymous. The information is never used to identify individuals.
BROWSER COOKIES: We may use "cookies" to store specific information about a member's account (if cookies are enabled in the member's browser). This cookie is a small file containing encrypted data pertinent to the member's account, such as their name and account number. The cookie is stored on the member's computer and cannot be viewed by others. The information contained in it is only used for storing account information for future visits.
MEMBER RECORDS: Member records are never sold to third parties and are only viewed by Run Wild Missoula staff when necessary.
SECURE TRANSACTIONS: This site uses a secure SSL server so information submitted by you in secure mode is encrypted for your privacy. This means no other party can view personal information while in transit over the Internet. Credit card transactions are completely safe using this technology.
Run Wild Missoula reserves the right to change its on-line policy at any time. Future changes will be duly noted on this page. If you have any other questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at any time.
RWM Social Media
EVENTS CALENDAR
UPCOMING EVENTS
Dec 15:  Tuesday Buddy RunDec 15:  Tuesday TrackDec 17:  Thursday Buddy RunDec 19:  Saturday Group RunDec 20:  Run for MissoulaDec 22:  Tuesday Buddy RunDec 22:  Tuesday TrackDec 24:  Thursday Buddy RunDec 26:  Saturday Group RunDec 29:  Tuesday Buddy RunDec 29:  Tuesday TrackDec 31:  Thursday Buddy RunDec 31:  Tony Banovich Memorial RunJan 01:  2021 Resolution RunJan 02:  Saturday Group RunJan 05:  Tuesday Buddy RunJan 05:  Tuesday TrackJan 07:  Thursday Buddy RunJan 09:  Saturday Group RunJan 12:  Tuesday Buddy RunJan 12:  Tuesday TrackJan 14:  Thursday Buddy RunJan 16:  Saturday Group RunJan 19:  Tuesday Buddy RunJan 19:  Tuesday TrackJan 21:  Thursday Buddy RunJan 23:  Saturday Group RunJan 26:  Tuesday Buddy RunJan 26:  Tuesday TrackJan 28:  Thursday Buddy RunJan 30:  Saturday Group RunFeb 02:  Tuesday Buddy RunFeb 02:  Tuesday TrackFeb 04:  Thursday Buddy RunFeb 06:  Saturday Group RunFeb 09:  Tuesday Buddy RunFeb 09:  Tuesday TrackFeb 11:  Thursday Buddy RunFeb 13:  Saturday Group RunFeb 16:  Tuesday Buddy RunFeb 16:  Tuesday TrackFeb 18:  Thursday Buddy RunView All Events »
LATEST NEWS
Member Spotlight: Sally HenkelPosted Wednesday, December 2, 2020Member Spotlight: Julie McCloskeyPosted Sunday, November 1, 2020Donation in Honor of Tony BanovichPosted Friday, October 16, 2020Ask A Coach: Increasing MileagePosted Monday, October 5, 2020Member Spotlight: 2020 Member Award WinnersPosted Wednesday, September 30, 2020
View All News »
TESTIMONIALS
"[The Missoula Marathon] gets better every year and I get to watch the progress. There is a certain amount of ownership, pride and boasting privilege one has when their community hosts a really exciting event. Missoula is my home by choice and events like this reinforce my decision."- Cynthia Wood, 48
